# DAVID MCGREGOR

#### **Full Stack Developer**

github.com/davmcgregor



## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a full-stack software developer currently working remotely with an emphasis on front end web development. A former digital communications specialist, my love of coding has grown from a passive interest to a full-fledged passion. Now I'm enjoying learning and challenging myself at every opportunity.

## **RECENT PROJECTS**

#### % Stoic Wisdom

PostgreSQL, Express, React, Node, TailwindCSS

Website and API that showcases quotes from the great stoic thinkers. Additional features include natural language processing, full-text search, and Mailgun integration.

#### % Covid-19 Tracker

React, Chart.js, Material UI

React app that makes an API call to display the latest Covid-19 statistics.

#### % Other Projects

Javascript, Ruby, Rails, HTML, CSS, TDD

Miscellaneous tech tests, tutorials, experiments and small projects can be found on my public Github.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Front End Developer

#### **Percipio**

May 2020 - Ongoing

**♀** London/Remote

Building websites and apps for the UK Education and Government Technology sectors, contributing to the development team and implementing UX and information design.

#### Various Digital Communications Roles

₩ Jun 2014 - Ongoing

**♀** Sydney/Melbourne/Brisbane

#### Accomplishments:

- Australian Army Reserve (Captain, Public Affairs Officer):
  Generated a range of communications material, including; media alerts, releases, training packages, video and photography.
- Australian Labor Party: Exceeded digital engagement targets by maintaining organic social reach at over 2 million views per week.
- Australian Republic Movement: Deployed a digital marketing architecture that increased membership by 3000% over 2 years.
- Australian Workers' Union: Managed digital campaigns, social media and stakeholder engagement.

## **TECH SKILLS**

Vue Redux Node.is React **Express TailwindCSS** Ruby Rails Craft CMS Docker PostgreSQL MongoDB **APIs AWS** Git Heroku Agile methodology Pair programming Test-driven development

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Modern React with Redux Udemy course by Stephen Grider

₩ 2020

Including NPM, Webpack, Babel, and ES6/ES2015 Javascript syntax

The Web Developer Bootcamp Udemy course by Colt Steele

**2019** 

Complete full-stack developer course including Node.js

#### **EDUCATION**

Software Developer Graduate Makers Academy

mar 2020 - Mar 2020

Selective 16-week coding course on software engineering fundamentals.

Juris Doctor

The University of Melbourne

# Jan 2010 - Mar 2013

Law Degree - admitted to practice 2015

Bachelor of Commerce

The University of Sydney

Majors in Economics and International Business